{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"5fe3e30d-7e55-4a72-8306-d6a4763a5f05"},"exam":{"id":"d5099a99-aba8-40e4-8fc6-0dde3549b4b6","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"porkjt4t-1idl-7vgv-mx2b-s6gvayouwvh4","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are advantages of cloud computing?","explanation":"Elasticity, Agility, and the ability to control the variances in your month-to-month expenditure are all advantages of the flexibility of Cloud Computing. You do still need specialist knowledge to deploy solutions in the Cloud, such as AWS Certifications. Large amounts of capital are also not needed due to the consumption model of most cloud services, although you can sometimes use capital expenditure to purchase resources for extended periods of time, such as Reserved Instances in EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0368a69e2586f302d0f3da6bfa3b031","text":"Agility - Decreasing the time to start new services","correct":true},{"id":"97e11cb086bf1070777e7e3fa1e31877","text":"Requires large amounts of capital","correct":false},{"id":"b6244c70b8f2eb23f7eb82a740202646","text":"No specialist knowledge required","correct":false},{"id":"e614fc350d8c3730eaca43265d43d9de","text":"Variable expense","correct":true},{"id":"230dee0a7da58ba8fbf9dee4e7448de2","text":"Elasticity - you need not worry about capacity.","correct":true}]},{"id":"c8b4a47e-2f35-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following classifications apply to AWS Organizations?","explanation":" AWS Organizations is classified as a Management and Governance tool because it is used to consolidate AWS accounts into an organization that you create and centrally manage.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_introduction.html","title":"What Is AWS Organizations?"}],"answers":[{"id":"091fa9121c047db1dd48c3e2ab5f3c91","text":"Machine Learning","correct":false},{"id":"5525aee13c9e8a25b1f35514f33ab825","text":"Security, Identity, and Compliance","correct":false},{"id":"492db50276b71e1628e9eb261d4f83b7","text":"Management and Governance","correct":true},{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false}]},{"id":"86d0ccb9-ab67-4952-a7ea-0fea12fc6c1f","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to data security in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which includes security. The customer is responsible for who can access the data itself.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"599dca975551e5a41106ce454a46e4e0","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":true},{"id":"9f02eb6c8050b89db31831403951787b","text":"The customer is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":true},{"id":"0ed894aaf38bd44ba33d1612854617d0","text":"AWS is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":false},{"id":"2844802845f801aded529f1d22c63d82","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":true},{"id":"7a0bc438686e10d5e1ab102d0dc0e4a9","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":false},{"id":"6e8271456f0c471167caae0d75aab487","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":false}]},{"id":"d54df537-f2ee-46a2-b1f4-2c115bdf2044","domain":"concepts","question":"Using Infrastructure as Code is a related of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Infrastructure as Code is a key implementation of Automation in cloud - using Infrastructure as Code allows to quickly and easily deploy and manage your environment without reliance on humans to complete all the tasks. Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, and it allows you to expand out as needed. Elasticity is the ability to go up and down in resources as needed. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":true},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"f3458221-d64a-4bbb-b337-65aa47b1614e","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following does Amazon assure will happen when paying for AWS on an as-needed basis?","explanation":"Amazon provides certain benefits when you pay for services on an as-needed basis for your business. You can spend more time innovating and inventing, which consequently reduces the complexity of procurement and enables your business to be fully elastic. ","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"805b488dc48f4591141569966cee0a89","text":"Enabling the full elasticity of business operations","correct":true},{"id":"4657fb4ee914ab51c07ee5913b69cb48","text":"Reducing procurement complexity","correct":true},{"id":"48a2453a766bcd12a90a271271ca86a5","text":"Redirecting focus to innovation and invention","correct":true},{"id":"d2c91d7ba7466b41bdbcd42e13db2ecb","text":"Spending more money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"8c0088e02946138166ef2d9e4bf9ab82","text":"Spending less money in the long term","correct":false}]},{"id":"ca0mnlws-zcum-4ktx-vhea-4j7tzi5qof7m","domain":"security","question":"What is the recommended way to give your applications running in EC2 permission to other AWS resources?","explanation":"You should use IAM Roles wherever possible to enable applications running on EC2 instances to access other AWS resources. This is the most secure method to do so. It is not possible to assign an IAM Group or User to an instance, and although using the Root Keys in you application would work this is HIGHLY insecure and should never be done, as the Root Keys have access to absolutely everything in your account.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/iam-roles-for-amazon-ec2.html","title":"IAM Roles for Amazon EC2"}],"answers":[{"id":"6bd8f4a2aff7022a330dc33c097a2f5a","text":"Create an IAM Role with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":true},{"id":"0bce771e576c7cf6bd90b9463d344860","text":"Create an IAM Group with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"d12b50f23d2457b811312e994c2569d0","text":"Create an IAM User with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"01943125f389f038045d6c0c56cafcce","text":"Create an Root Access Key and use it in the application.","correct":false}]},{"id":"80c462fa-2fa6-11ea-aec2-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support plans provide access to online self-paced labs for training staff?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan provides access to online self-paced labs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false}]},{"id":"c6jepoji-nqyo-0t96-juj8-ob2lymloevj9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Assurance Program?","explanation":"Certifications/Attestations and Compliance with Laws and Regulations are cornerstones of the of the AWS Assurance Program.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Assurance"}],"answers":[{"id":"fc0d934854b825185d4ea2079edf68c3","text":"Compliance with Laws and Regulations","correct":true},{"id":"de208db5a32df9befe2ed7f080863f9e","text":"Customer Testimonials","correct":false},{"id":"4dc626268903b46b79d0a76e0a989cf8","text":"Partner Validations","correct":false},{"id":"19d78b92947f957cca4c7698118fdb82","text":"Following industry best practices","correct":false},{"id":"506afacef0a47cc7635b5cf0a3476c31","text":"Certifications/Attestations","correct":true}]},{"id":"71sehgn8-lx4k-034j-srs9-vv6xhd7w10qh","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to performance efficiency?","explanation":"Of these choices, you should democratize advanced technologies, deploy into multiple Regions, and use Serverless technologies.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"db3e408a0aa09a4e83bdace8a1e57fcc","text":"Deploy into multiple Regions to go global in minutes.","correct":true},{"id":"56110ec02fe5d9a3ae8e5a69af838158","text":"Have your IT staff master all new technologies.","correct":false},{"id":"c25dea02447eef08ddb2affdbb171485","text":"Mechanical empathy","correct":false},{"id":"e891a453952de1898dde71f36801790a","text":"Use Serverless architectures.","correct":true},{"id":"8c3a4b8048462b1877e2da598308fe3a","text":"Democratize advanced technologies.","correct":true}]},{"id":"4885465a-c1a0-41e2-8e7d-d6ac27557522","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following comprises an Amazon Machine Image (AMI)?","explanation":"An AMI includes three types of information. There’s the Amazon EBS snapshot or snapshots for backing up EBS volume data to S3, or a template for the root volume of the instance if the AMI is instance-store-backed. There are launch permissions for controlling which AWS accounts can use the AMI to launch an instance. And there’s block device mapping for specifying the volumes to attach to the instance when it’s launched. These are the pieces of information that AMI requires to launch an EC2 instance; the EC2 instance is part of the AMI itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/WindowsGuide/AMIs.html","title":"Amazon Machine Images (AMI) – Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"6f8a7b69b94bd2a5b6d397b35bf7a403","text":"EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"11d5f5efdfcf29972a22321321560da7","text":"EBS snapshots or root volume template of an EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"1dd2a814eff8bee8cf3e4da0ee6a245e","text":"Block device mapping","correct":true},{"id":"fb7756bd7b1e9872836772b73ccf9aac","text":"Launch permissions","correct":true}]},{"id":"3617c0aa-2fa9-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"For enhanced technical support, some AWS Support plans enable you to have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases. Which of the following choices offer this feature?","explanation":"With either the Business or Enterprise support plan, you can provide have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"3lwo2qi6-7yzt-o86p-u1vg-vxwsbedkzwt0","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the Security Pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework?","explanation":"IAM, Detective Controls and Infrastructure Protection are key parts of the Security Pillar of the Well Archtiected Framwork. IAM - ensuring that only authorized and authenticated users are able to access your resources. Detective Controls to identify a potential security threat or incident. Infrastructure Protection covers the control methodologies, such as defense in depth, necessary to meet best practices and organizational or regulatory obligations.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/architecture/well-architected/","title":"The Well-Architected FRamework"}],"answers":[{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"b9237ed805ea2fe23003f7e73fc1f7d4","text":"Detective Controls","correct":true},{"id":"d5552e0564007d93ff5937a9cb3bc491","text":"Customer Service","correct":false},{"id":"a571cb3f6a39b87e03d60bce4e086f6c","text":"Technical Account Management","correct":false},{"id":"96c4db3cd9b4be5b89474dff6d0fe9b1","text":"Infrastructure protection","correct":true}]},{"id":"9635210d-5701-4697-a1c1-43d560757b8f","domain":"billing","question":"When would you use the EC2 On Demand pricing model?","explanation":"You would use the EC2 On Demand model when you need compute capability that does not require any up front payments or long term commitments, and where you have applications with short term or unpredictable workloads that cannot be interrupted.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"e6f9ef5372dbb1435dcf5572384518a0","text":"No upfront payments required","correct":true},{"id":"fd379e462843bd9411eeb4d620576dae","text":"Unpredictable workloads that cannot be interrupted","correct":true},{"id":"745e16b69cf097a0be4ccb8e3a7e1a39","text":"Discounted cost model compared to Reserved Instances ","correct":false},{"id":"6f30c21b296170a18a7b5b51e1b41463","text":"Guaranteed cost","correct":false}]},{"id":"zlyf2s8s-kula-sxtl-s07a-i3uh455n1hnu","domain":"security","question":"Which credentials can you use to access the AWS Management console?","explanation":"You use a username and password to log into the AWS console, although Access key and Secret Access key can be used to access some APIs programmatically","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"The AWS Management Console"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a7454c71a60c06ab2189283f1788e09","text":"Your Secret Access key","correct":false},{"id":"4dd4dfb52929ef230415ada1a4169dc1","text":"Your Security Token","correct":false},{"id":"be677306ceb7d966e7a06ee1bf387acf","text":"Your Access key","correct":false},{"id":"afc76c6d8222878e0449abb2ea16838f","text":"Your Username and Password","correct":true}]},{"id":"wzp94cj7-nvoj-2owh-4pxj-hrbz8160358x","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are criteria affecting your billing for RDS?","explanation":"RDS runs on EC2 instances, so much like an EC2 instance, you are charged based on how long the RDS instances are running, how much storage they have provisioned, and the requests they're processing. Standard monitoring is included for free with RDS instances, although Enhanced Monitoring is available for more information. Data Transfer in to RDS, like most other AWS services, is free","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"a2c4368093f9a13bd6548416cca5570c","text":"Running duration of the RDS instances","correct":true},{"id":"a817cbcc67f9a1988581b7d71d401622","text":"Number of requests","correct":true},{"id":"f7b3ef9e030e62319f8b3b42154eb67f","text":"Additional storage","correct":true},{"id":"c2b89d380496f89ae6f7baf5d69be55f","text":"Standard monitoring services","correct":false},{"id":"f7f231f31a2c9b561fe0b7963e550e6a","text":"Data transfer in","correct":false}]},{"id":"123bb9de-8d93-4feb-81c0-d4e85038cd47","domain":"tech","question":"When setting up the properties of an S3 bucket, which of the following options should you select to get detailed records for the requests made to the bucket?","explanation":"Server access logging is what you should select to record and get information on the requests made to your bucket. Object-level logging, sometimes referred to as S3 CloudTrail logging, saves all API events performed on the S3 bucket in json format.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/ServerLogs.html","title":"Amazon S3 Server Access Logging"}],"answers":[{"id":"189f63f277cd73395561651753563065","text":"Tags","correct":false},{"id":"f87d839acefa86eff3c90b1b44be4aba","text":"Object-level logging","correct":false},{"id":"198a30920479d1d8e2509b9b59f3d700","text":"Versioning","correct":false},{"id":"30054ccc9b587d53668a89942396874c","text":"Server access logging","correct":true}]},{"id":"cd73d505-c09a-44cb-a7fa-0ac6be0f5c99","domain":"tech","question":"Upon attempting to create an additional S3 bucket, you realize that you have reached your S3 bucket limit in your AWS account. You anticipate creating even more S3 buckets in the future for your photos and documents. Which of the following is the quickest solution?","explanation":"The key word here is 'quickest'. Granted, you can delete the S3 buckets of your choice, and you can try consolidating files into select buckets and deleting the emptied ones. But that could be quite a hassle to do, compared to simply requesting a service limit increase at the AWS Support Center. By default, you can create up to 100 buckets in an AWS account, and that is a limit that AWS does not override without officially requesting for a service limit increase.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"340d5ba6fcedb315c6adee97b1239f3f","text":"Consolidate files into half of the S3 buckets and delete the empty ones.","correct":false},{"id":"e7b93b6f7bea9c58f27912c7974c74d4","text":"Submit a service limit increase.","correct":true},{"id":"46bca3e00e40780aa04c28899f5bbe6b","text":"Simply create the S3 bucket; AWS will automatically override the bucket limit.","correct":false},{"id":"104e2902668d313ccfbc1bc78457e84d","text":"Delete the S3 buckets that you barely use.","correct":false}]},{"id":"01355a86-1c9a-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"In Amazon EC2, which of the following do you use to log into Linux instances?","explanation":"To log into Linux instances using EC2, you will need a key pair; Windows instances are the ones that need a user name and password to log in. Multi-factor authentication (MFA) involves the addition of an extra layer of protection, such as a code generated from an authenticator, to a user name and password. MFA can be enabled to use with IAM, or Identity and Access Management.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_security-outside-iam.html","title":"Security Features Outside of IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"1a504cebc3822fd967eb6426a7ff0a31","text":"Multi-factor authentication","correct":false},{"id":"f3499a9f28ab4d9412f8dc5e818c8ccd","text":"User name and password","correct":false},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":false},{"id":"6cd56a4cc4ddbbfd2bc9d57de5d788aa","text":"Key pair","correct":true}]},{"id":"su6exaen-uvfq-awbs-r1m3-y06rtjhsbaw6","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services can help you assess the fault-tolerance of your AWS environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor can help you assess the fault-tolerance of your AWS environment. AWS Inspector can help you assess your security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false}]},{"id":"qlfvvg3n-igqt-be79-1bph-rx4nrjmqmm25","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below statements are correct in relation to security responsibilities in AWS?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud - the security of components that run the cloud service. The customer is responsible for security IN the cloud -- that is, the security of their AWS resources and data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"a1b79685a2bbdb6743277416ad663c24","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"d1f8c47a806feef1c562619b465cb202","text":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"7c5f3942078ece3769cd1bcbde2bdabb","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"0369ed76a5e4ccb3887e44fe8a7c8703","text":"AWS is responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"97909ec2-34ad-4743-b7cc-ca2c83c62cc1","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"The AWS Free Tier offers some services for free for the first 12 months after signing up for an AWS account. It also offers free trials of select AWS services for a short period. So, usage is governed by these principles. Although there are some service usages that are always free, this does not apply to EC2 Micro instances nor S3 storage of up to 5 GB.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"c90c4c865ee803cfa9bbe8e9a2d845c9","text":"Amazon S3 storage of up to 5 GB is always free.","correct":false},{"id":"42c6d3d9032dba4f7aea8ddeedde2f6c","text":"You will never be charged for use of EC2 Micro instances.","correct":false},{"id":"424553c7a1502a98737dfd15823ee215","text":"Some AWS services are free for the first 12 months following the initial sign-up date to AWS.","correct":true},{"id":"f60585d833d73cf82fda96da1f19b3e6","text":"Some AWS services come with short-term free trial offers.","correct":true}]},{"id":"04uew9ya-7pbn-ugmi-3vzh-1erxijop26v7","domain":"billing","question":"You are an AWS Enterprise customer with questions about billing and your overall AWS account. Which of the following AWS support personnel should you contact?","explanation":"For AWS Enterprise customers, the AWS Concierge is a resource dedicated to answering billing and account questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/features/","title":"AWS Support Features"}],"answers":[{"id":"0037cad42801741c9acb59d7d7ba9a5f","text":"AWS Billing and Accounts","correct":false},{"id":"aebccaafe1827e1ed91b1d9a27dac4a8","text":"AWS Technical Account Manager","correct":false},{"id":"26e8220e8fac28d2a1a9a18ca81aabd7","text":"AWS Support","correct":false},{"id":"bac90b5cd782c7dc092efa042af32e5c","text":"AWS Concierge","correct":true}]},{"id":"338d1783-ff92-46f0-b582-c4bb314efcff","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is the collection of tools used for developing and managing applications on AWS?","explanation":"Software Development Kits, or SDKs, provide everything you need to develop and manage applications in AWS, including the programming language of your choice.","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-overview.pdf","title":"Overview of Amazon Web Services"}],"answers":[{"id":"4b77a7b9a57e83d2c4b01e16f3234143","text":"Command Line Interface","correct":false},{"id":"a3b73fb1194d31eec199838e4fc4c08a","text":"AWS Management Console","correct":false},{"id":"41942dbedbefdea8b52c300f0dc777d0","text":"Programming Languages","correct":false},{"id":"0654ac3bb453dcb388c05bee59caa0be","text":"Software Development Kits","correct":true}]},{"id":"bfoxiudd-ep8s-9jah-t2ho-96nct3a3mjfh","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following data archival services is extremely inexpensive, but can have a multi-hour data-retrieval window?","explanation":"Glacier offers extremely inexpensive data archival, but requires a 3-5 hour data-retrieval window for standard retrievals - though this time can be reduced for a price. Other S3 storage tiers, including Infrequent Access (S3-IA) can all be accessed immediately, but some may incur additional fees for accessing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/","title":"About Glacier"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/storage-classes/?nc=sn&loc=3","title":"S3 Storage Classes"}],"answers":[{"id":"4def2a084469f97f6372bfaf0823941b","text":"Glacier","correct":true},{"id":"4340570ba672bfa48cd45e3f026c01d1","text":"S3 - IA","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"31e831ec49678aed7f467f791d1f8704","text":"S3 - RRS","correct":false},{"id":"e9a5105fa288ef2b71c037e42d665d91","text":"S3 - OneZone-IA","correct":false}]},{"id":"pdd3afvz-mr6t-zycv-zdle-ceeorrmdl4o9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program?","explanation":"Control Environment, Risk Management and Information Security are all components of the AWS Risk and Compliance Program. Control Environment includes policies, processes and control activities that are in place to secure the delivery of AWS’ service offerings. AWS management has developed a strategic business plan which includes risk identification and the implementation of controls to mitigate or manage risks as part of the Risk Management component. AWS has implemented a formal information security program designed to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of customers’ systems and data.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/compliance/AWS_Risk_and_Compliance_Whitepaper.pdf","title":"AWS Risk and Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"0719bdee85b7a37d4e74a9d542d24861","text":" Physical Security","correct":false},{"id":"791716f366839a73d41b8ac1ae95bad0","text":"Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"0889f4cee1d9f42ae2c1daf686377de0","text":"Information Security","correct":true},{"id":"66216159eaf3a0abb2752836096f99e9","text":"Security Principles","correct":false},{"id":"74f53be5e22fad65f914f82977df2447","text":"Control Environment","correct":true},{"id":"b8aba77333d3fc881739506fee08811c","text":"Environment Automation","correct":false},{"id":"7228bb53bb7855d458965d2f15fc6cd7","text":"Risk Management","correct":true}]},{"id":"5d3e351c-1f62-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following constitute Multi-Factor Authentication for signing into the AWS Management Console?","explanation":"Multi-factor authentication, or MFA, adds an extra layer of protection to your user name and password when logging in to the AWS Management Console. To sign in, you would need two factors, which are 1.) the user name and password; and 2.) an authentication code from an AWS-supported MFA software app.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/features/mfa/","title":"IAM - Multi-factor Authentication"}],"answers":[{"id":"f3499a9f28ab4d9412f8dc5e818c8ccd","text":"User name and password","correct":false},{"id":"59f2c8e6be7c2804d73e2f0bad9b26e8","text":"User name, password, and authentication code","correct":true},{"id":"36562a3012cb05bd90eed776b4760dc7","text":"User name and authentication code","correct":false},{"id":"4cf20b6f419df88d662bb7d18bd7c7e1","text":"Password and authentication code","correct":false}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false},{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true},{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false}]},{"id":"86ed7d54-4495-435b-908a-b439c255c35d","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the five best practices does AWS Trusted Advisor use to eliminate unused, underutilized, and idle resources in your environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor ensures cost optimization of your AWS account by eliminating unused, underutilized, and idle resources, which include EC2 instances, load balancers, EBS volumes, and elastic IP addresses.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor Best Practice Checks"}],"answers":[{"id":"07d2fdfae089a6e085811b22437de261","text":"Service limits","correct":false},{"id":"45a75e44a713fdf94dbf1dbaa0749188","text":"Fault tolerance","correct":false},{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":false},{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":false},{"id":"a39ae09f8be4327fc176cfeb76a0e366","text":"Cost optimization","correct":true}]},{"id":"7ed103d1-670b-487f-aa14-6d5e29084eb2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following Amazon EC2 pricing models automatically adjusts charges as your usage changes?","explanation":"Savings Plans is the only Amazon EC2 pricing model that provides the flexibility of adjusting charges depending on the amount of usage, thereby saving money in the process.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/savingsplans/","title":"Savings Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"b9912bfb6c79dc963ccc7e74d0ef9b36","text":"Savings Plan","correct":true},{"id":"29068f6044e3fedf44165e646a2d2bb1","text":"Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":false},{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":false}]},{"id":"4d895136-18cf-11ea-b8f0-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"ElastiCache is an example of what type of AWS Services?","explanation":"ElastiCache is an in-memory cache service used to improve database performance. This means that it saves your most common queries for quicker data retrieval rather than retrieving directly from your database. As a result, it is classified as an AWS database service.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticache/","title":"Amazon ElastiCache"}],"answers":[{"id":"8c4aa541ee911e8d80451ef8cc304806","text":"Storage","correct":false},{"id":"a768caa988605a2846599cf7e2d0c26a","text":"Analytics","correct":false},{"id":"e307db07b3975fef922a80d07455ee5e","text":"Database","correct":true},{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false}]},{"id":"30rp7hn8-3uti-zql0-ays0-x3qfjnnnaax9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones?","explanation":"A Region is a geographic area that hosts two or more Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"0ed2343b7ec3f778399e20cf93f8f507","text":"Compute Zones","correct":false},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false}]},{"id":"561b98dd-beb4-4111-8cb8-b5609a124873","domain":"tech","question":"What benefits can CloudFront bring to your e-commerce website?","explanation":"CloudFront provides the ability to cache both static and dynamic content in 200 points of presence located around the world, ensuring quick response times can be had by customers when retrieving cached website content. This inclueds protections with AWS WAF and AWS Shield. No additional analytics will necessarily be available, nor is CloudFront a database solution","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/features/","title":"Amazon CloudFront Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"286fe6e5d97e4ad18aac77cef2b5e28c","text":"Increased application availability","correct":true},{"id":"6c47d5971e79af6daf2b24070bd1e8ac","text":"Scalable managed database which integrates seamlessly with Lambda and EC2","correct":false},{"id":"61c592ef1e234bfa1834570f2238d22f","text":"Advanced analytics into customer journeys","correct":false},{"id":"3559eb841146fbbde9ede18594e319f1","text":"Protection against network and application layer attacks via WAF","correct":true},{"id":"bb42b85b5fcfff06d034f3102a1daa9e","text":"Lower latency for customers of your e-commerce website","correct":true}]},{"id":"ltl6jev0-2f05-xevd-rnut-yi3l7ar7nzk1","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to reliability?","explanation":"The elasticity of cloud computing means that you never need to over-provision or manage change at the resource level.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"2c081b2e4ef662d134361511c0f138e1","text":"Manage change at the individual resource level.","correct":false},{"id":"25ddbfce9d53b8f5a9e09aad85948b96","text":"Stop guessing about your capacity requirements.","correct":true},{"id":"c57c5e34d89769a30ca48ef1c1155033","text":"Scale horizontally.","correct":true},{"id":"7f20528f07a394778f02e20e5453fc02","text":"When in doubt, over-provision.","correct":false}]},{"id":"pnvuqf5l-037m-d7re-80px-dktopvvnrkq4","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services should you use to migrate an existing database to AWS?","explanation":"The AWS Database Migration Service is a service specifically designed to support migrations of databases from on-premise into AWS","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/dms/","title":"About the AWS Database Migration Service"}],"answers":[{"id":"0893147538c21c827dc499b4852934e3","text":"Route 53","correct":false},{"id":"54afc4697cf03d8e3ec9a05b16380622","text":"SNS","correct":false},{"id":"947642228a6d69446c74618fdde1bfd6","text":"Storage Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"1d61150ca8c56343cc23363e78429886","text":"AWS DMS","correct":true}]},{"id":"06891e46-1d7d-4ec7-9866-e5c980901ca8","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true about the Amazon EC2 service?","explanation":"All statements are correct except one. EC2 does not limit the maximum number of virtual servers to 5; you can launch as many of them as you need.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/concepts.html","title":"What Is Amazon EC2?"}],"answers":[{"id":"8f29ef75026ce095e4c2bdfef7fda8d4","text":"It provides virtual computing environments.","correct":true},{"id":"4e9a1f08edd0d2fc4013ed10e09f571c","text":"It is used to launch up to 5 servers.","correct":false},{"id":"f24b25808e75812b13593ad35b4e87c0","text":"It provides scalable computing capacity in the AWS cloud.","correct":true},{"id":"05abe36774fd4ff06a9e3dbea47f091b","text":"It supplies various configurations of CPU, memory, storage, and network capacity.","correct":true}]},{"id":"d7507bdc-1a47-11ea-9fef-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"What is the default limit for the number of network ACLs in a VPC?","explanation":"You can associate up to 200 network ACLs in each VPC.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/amazon-vpc-limits.html","title":"Amazon VPC Limits"}],"answers":[{"id":"94f6d7e04a4d452035300f18b984988c","text":"300","correct":false},{"id":"f899139df5e1059396431415e770c6dd","text":"100","correct":false},{"id":"18d8042386b79e2c279fd162df0205c8","text":"400","correct":false},{"id":"3644a684f98ea8fe223c713b77189a77","text":"200","correct":true}]},{"id":"1s9oou1o-9lmx-321m-4ite-iqy9x7zuv18y","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed database service that is compatible with MySQL, but provides better performance?","explanation":"Aurora is AWS' managed database service that is up to 5X faster than a traditional MySQL database. PostgreSQL, DynamoDB, and MariaDB are all different database technologies which are not directly compatible with MySQL","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/","title":"About Aurora"}],"answers":[{"id":"7f9733e208088b1ce6df3d4be1765396","text":"MariaDB","correct":false},{"id":"509e0895bd82e3315e79018a6ce02181","text":"Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"399bd1ee587245ecac6f39beaa99886f","text":"PostgreSQL","correct":false}]},{"id":"e08137aa-20a0-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following describes a subnet?","explanation":"A virtual private cloud, or VPC, is the virtual network you create in your AWS account. When you create a VPC, you split it into smaller network segments by specifying a range of IP addresses. These segments are referred to as subnets, and this is where you launch your AWS resources.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"5e57bdce4ee3d720c44022ab3a1989dc","text":"A virtual network dedicated to an AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"79da4a3447f86eaa72f611a8d8a1d4cc","text":"A private connection to the virtual private cloud","correct":false},{"id":"341f92e23cc01405941735e106cc5b82","text":"A range of IP addresses in the virtual private cloud","correct":true},{"id":"35b8947d693a814719c463b699fee868","text":"A subsection of the Internet","correct":false}]},{"id":"wdqr2l66-jcd9-o6lx-b012-qodibilagwi2","domain":"tech","question":"You need to implement an automated service that will scan your AWS environment with the goal of both improving security and reducing costs. Which service should you use?","explanation":"An online resource to help you reduce cost, increase performance, and improve security by optimizing your AWS environment, Trusted Advisor provides real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"0bcfa28115476b2bcfed146f27c465c4","text":"Service Catalog","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"9633b701743bf40ce928fb9fa4c0ed66","text":"Config Rules","correct":false}]},{"id":"5a9b87ae-3552-46ad-9cee-605c6dc2d534","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS services can be used to create billing alarms?","explanation":"The CloudWatch service is used to create billing alarms. The Cost Explorer service is used to creates custom reports that facilitate the understanding of the organization's costs and data usage. Macie is a service used to identify sensitive data such as personally identifiable information (PII) stored in S3. The Athena service analyzes data using SQL queries stored in S3.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudWatch/latest/monitoring/monitor_estimated_charges_with_cloudwatch.html","title":"Creating a Billing Alarm to Monitor Your Estimated AWS Charges"}],"answers":[{"id":"582ca45acfd3e21caca8b786c1413850","text":"Athena","correct":false},{"id":"689485d385032d81c9cc43cbc981549a","text":"Macie","correct":false},{"id":"619ed6d20397878e9706fe9fa7c44579","text":"Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":true}]},{"id":"b6f1e02c-1a49-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS CloudTrail?","explanation":"CloudTrail is actually enabled automatically when you create an AWS account. The other three responses are correct.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awscloudtrail/latest/userguide/how-cloudtrail-works.html","title":"How CloudTrail Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"c4817f75e8865468e0d6688b3f7fa9ae","text":"CloudTrail delivers log files within 15 minutes of account activity.","correct":true},{"id":"38105bf4ed77d230d01428de259f3ea0","text":"By default, CloudTrail event log files are encrypted using Amazon S3 server-side encryption.","correct":true},{"id":"98be3a0e01d49274c41618e1b43ff9c5","text":"When you create an AWS account, you will have to manually enable CloudTrail.","correct":false},{"id":"d70f308061c9f3b0aef10fe5b3a954ab","text":"With CloudTrail, you can create a trail that either applies to one Region or to all Regions.","correct":true}]},{"id":"5l7vjhuv-wf9j-de1i-9aj4-e9dlg8u6cc76","domain":"billing","question":"Your Development team uses four on-demand EC2 instances, and your QA team has 5 reserved instances, only three of which are being used. Assuming all AWS accounts are under a single AWS Organization, how will the Development team's instances be billed?","explanation":"Assuming all instances are in the same AWS Organization, the reserved instance pricing for the unused QA instances will be applied to two of the four Dev instances.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/pricing/","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"b04b07a9c68b5b505f53afccb5616743","text":"The pricing for the reserved instances will shift from QA to Dev.","correct":false},{"id":"3ea9a50157f205cce00d0db169117711","text":"All the Dev instances will be billed at the reserved instance rate.","correct":false},{"id":"a6d19cc18b59af08baaa0f8247fca355","text":"The Dev team will be billed for two instances at on-demand prices and two instances at the reserved instance price.","correct":true},{"id":"ecadbc09799c3807dfed5bd9ee9c6159","text":"All the Dev team's instances will be billed at the on-demand rate.","correct":false}]},{"id":"1u986u6j-pa4x-orum-u2t7-qu0b9lljqm76","domain":"tech","question":"You need to ensure that you have the correct number of EC2 instances available to handle the load for your application. Which AWS service should you use?","explanation":"Auto Scaling will ensure you have the optimal number of EC2 instances to handle your application's load, based on rules you specify. The other services mentioned can help distribute load amongst existing resources, but do not have the ability by themselves to create new resources.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"e95e5a2a3cc8625bca3d71b817367e2d","text":"Elastic Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"b3b5475001f327d331389c6f07ff7c3a","text":"Application Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"afd14eb3f151c84e6ef7ab63812b4fbc","text":"Auto Scaling","correct":true}]},{"id":"afcc3e72-18ce-11ea-b8f0-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"If you want access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks, which of these support plans will provide that?","explanation":"You must choose either the Business or Enterprise support plan to gain access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"c2f17cbb-c270-426b-9312-2e5b0ed2b32c","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following database migrations are classified as heterogenous?","explanation":"In heterogenous database migrations, the source and target databases tend to be different in schema structure, data type, and database code. So, to simplify migration from Oracle and Microsoft SQL Server to Amazon Aurora, AWS automatically converts the source database schema and most of the custom code to a format compatible with Aurora. By contrast, Amazon RDS includes Oracle Database as one of its database engines, and Aurora is MySQL-compatible, so a migration from Oracle to Amazon RDS for Oracle or MySQL to Aurora is straightforward and does not need a conversion.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"Amazon RDS"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/","title":"Amazon Aurora"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/dms/","title":"AWS Database Migration"}],"answers":[{"id":"8cfffb1f6f5bfb85dae8b92ae8b1a1fa","text":"Oracle to Amazon Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"4c8e638aed3a82bf4024b088487c5ff7","text":"MySQL to Amazon Aurora","correct":false},{"id":"69923ac784b64e6a0719080837ad7d31","text":"Oracle to Amazon RDS for Oracle","correct":false},{"id":"fe2b9abea260f2445909c9cb6930e5b4","text":"Microsoft SQL Server to Amazon Aurora","correct":true}]},{"id":"27ohq41k-k7qp-a4r2-2r7m-05za454l4hk3","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers 24x7 support via phone or chat?","explanation":"The Business and Enterprise support plans, the two most expensive plans, offer 24 X 7 support via phone or chat. Neither of the other support plans (Basic and Developer) offer Phone support. Individual is also not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false}]},{"id":"4hjaxq6n-z5w0-zfz5-rhia-l14kd19r6656","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are best practices when it comes to securing your AWS account?","explanation":"Creating individual IAM users, using groups to assign them permission and creating a strong password policy are all key components of securing your AWS account. The root user should only be used in emergencies, therefore there should be no need to have Root Access Keys which allow the root user Programmatic access - any Programmatic access should use something other than the root account. It is not possible to delete the root password, and this should be securely, safely stored and not used in any applications!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"9c2eddf5402bf5f69b4cfd6f6cbb82ef","text":"Store your Root account keys on your application for easy access.","correct":false},{"id":"af5257e2e32921faab688050c9de091e","text":"Apply an IAM password policy.","correct":true},{"id":"427d69ad60aa7d9c68a9214e103fc80a","text":"Delete your Root account password.","correct":false},{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"561f3fa869736d8c37dd07fc1284f00f","text":"Delete your Root access keys.","correct":true},{"id":"5d44464e3d76ef6a6641b8044d7d2525","text":"Activate MFA on the Root Account.","correct":true},{"id":"07623cbc5a5f07bde8c94a98256a165f","text":"Use groups to assign permissions.","correct":true}]},{"id":"332dccb8-1a46-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following CIDR block size ranges applies to IPv4 addresses in Amazon VPC?","explanation":"For IPv4 addresses, the VPC CIDR block size can be anywhere from /16 to /28.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/vpc-ip-addressing.html","title":"IP Addressing in Your VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"699292f46538d2bf62bace8334097bb6","text":"1/ to /40","correct":false},{"id":"30575066a7baaedf5c35a22bc44a6964","text":"/16 to /28","correct":true},{"id":"b23abf46c1e7e117251291617bac5c56","text":"/8 to /36","correct":false},{"id":"d312bf1a99a33142c6a946375494aa20","text":"/12 to /32","correct":false}]},{"id":"e3b24121-862f-4b1e-8f4e-18e6f3f9e1e8","domain":"concepts","question":"VMware Cloud on AWS allows companies to migrate and extend their on-premises VMware vSphere-based environments to AWS Cloud using Amazon EC2. Which of the following choices accurately classifies this deployment model?","explanation":"Hybrid deployments connect infrastructure and applications between cloud-based resources and existing resources that are not located in the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is an example of a hybrid deployment, since it involves the on-premises environments of VMware and the cloud-based services of AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","title":"Hybrid Cloud with AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"fb1b6e23a3767d2a31ef7899e6dd3f1e","text":"Hybrid","correct":true},{"id":"d6eb128e4c8971dc397f021585391999","text":"Shared Services","correct":false},{"id":"0fca8d17afc46bb08bd2d70a26cdf886","text":"On-Premises","correct":false},{"id":"c8e2277ecfb1427838c488c217f99466","text":"Cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false},{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false},{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true},{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false}]},{"id":"cfea2363-9af8-4536-b812-8ea53c44b11b","domain":"security","question":"You just had a Data Analyst join the company, and you have been tasked with creating a new IAM user accordingly. Although the user has received all the necessary credentials, she realized that she cannot perform any Amazon RDS actions on the Clients table. Which of the following are possible solutions to this issue?","explanation":"By default, an IAM user can’t access anything in the AWS account. So, the inability to perform the RDS actions on the Clients table is not a technical or password issue. To grant the permission to do so, you would need to create an identity-based policy. However, if there is a group in the account with the permission policy that will grant such access, you can add the user to that group instead.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_access-management.html","title":"Overview of Access Management: Permissions and Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"f46d75eb223838121ca6bec9ca08eaaa","text":"Create a ticket for the Help Desk to resolve the issue.","correct":false},{"id":"2f96bead1d7909e64836767c4e098acd","text":"Create an identity-based policy.","correct":true},{"id":"1971cb80efb016ad4254e3847a847434","text":"Supply the password necessary to log into the AWS console.","correct":false},{"id":"7731c1bfd28c89eee71012d973fa5407","text":"Double-check the credentials you sent to the user.","correct":false},{"id":"94412f8679d11dc0613f571ca4fba16b","text":"Add the user to the group that has the necessary permissions policy.","correct":true}]},{"id":"03ec629e-2f3a-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following includes components such as AWS Cost Explorer and AWS Budgets?","explanation":"AWS Cost Management consolidates tools that help you access, organize, understand, control, and optimize costs and usage in the cloud. These tools include Cost Explorer for visualizing and analyzing your expenses. They also include Budgets for creating budgets and getting automatic alerts when your costs or usage exceed or are expected to exceed the set thresholds.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/aws-cost-management/","title":"AWS Cost Management"}],"answers":[{"id":"c92b59d331719f616526d493633f5f74","text":"End User Computing","correct":false},{"id":"8c4aa541ee911e8d80451ef8cc304806","text":"Storage","correct":false},{"id":"5525aee13c9e8a25b1f35514f33ab825","text":"Security, Identity, and Compliance","correct":false},{"id":"4e0c7fb2fac186d1b3b5afd0fe2c278a","text":"Cost Management","correct":true}]},{"id":"eaf197bf-a9f1-4611-90be-dbcf7364c74a","domain":"concepts","question":"You have an application load balancer for routing traffic from developers to the EC2 instance that contains a web application being put into operation. To prepare for the application going live for public use, you add an Auto Scaling Group and a second application load balancer to route web traffic from customers to the EC2 instance. The addition is an example of which of the following:","explanation":"This is an example of scalability, which means that systems are expected to grow over time with no drop in performance. ","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"820b8f74ad843d1574106ec4cadfc07e","text":"Reliability","correct":false},{"id":"2166e76dc88d642260416a536b06a412","text":"Durability","correct":false}]},{"id":"2cp5w12s-zexu-46ts-0im3-vuthjxgjujs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used?","explanation":"Elasticity describes the ability to scale computing resources up or down easily, while only paying for the resources used.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":true},{"id":"fb76c61f626c7fb0fd2ee1226e9fd8bd","text":"Fault-tolerance","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false}]},{"id":"a6f49f26-0fbc-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for Amazon RDS?","explanation":"You can pay for Amazon RDS using either On-Demand or Reserved instance pricing.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"bda9eb7fcdccf237f87fb190ee3b4275","text":"Dedicated Server","correct":false},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"6c9d6b8aea6f3d16847bdebe05878a2d","text":"Spot","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The company’s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the company’s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true},{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false},{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false},{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false}]},{"id":"35f041db-16e3-4bb3-825d-7ab528bddd1b","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following falls under AWS compute services category?","explanation":"EC2, Lightsail, and Elastic Beanstalk fall under the compute umbrella of AWS services. EFS and AWS Backup are classified as storage services, and Amazon RDS is classified as database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"ce52d2cff6e50f2e74505e0c70d072b3","text":"AWS Backup","correct":false},{"id":"ce1a41ee0352cee512475ef6a6233963","text":"Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2)","correct":true},{"id":"98492fcf8e38ae7ea331e271498d5275","text":"Amazon Relational Database Services (RDS)","correct":false},{"id":"765c63bdfc41e7ae2614191faa2b0d0a","text":"Amazon Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"d2a6652ddeb631da029d1f2806e11fdc","text":"Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)","correct":false},{"id":"9e10649cd5a6507c47e44a66dc03eb5b","text":"Amazon Lightsail","correct":true}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false},{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false}]},{"id":"d05a0228-8d82-4cef-8dfb-4e2cb3856a9f","domain":"security","question":"According to the Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is AWS responsible for?","explanation":"Protecting the infrastructure that runs all of the services in the AWS Cloud is the responsibility of AWS. Such services include EC2 infrastructure - the hardware compute platform for running EC2 instances and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud, or VPC, which enables customers to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud to launch their resources. The subnets, security groups, and network access control lists configured in the VPC are the responsibility of the customer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"28aaf85b7ba1e63aa22c1c645a4c22e4","text":"Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) infrastructure","correct":true},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":true}]},{"id":"b9e84187-a101-b202-89a5-c5882d80f712","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Patch Management is a Shared Control, since AWS is responsible for patching and fixing flaws within the infrastructure, including managed services like RDS, but customers are responsible for patching their guest OS and applications. Firmware Upgrades, and other Hardware maintenance processes are solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of Security Groups remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"9ce46290f3196adff1535137f5fc1ee9","text":"Firmware Upgrades","correct":false},{"id":"c57c1a92dac4991db4fa1bca1517cca0","text":"Hardware Maintanence","correct":false},{"id":"474eabe8590389108f1fc92c9435c405","text":"Security Group Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"5d8e5aef41d3dab7bda43eaace3a2a06","text":"Patch Management","correct":true}]},{"id":"4rfhb5p7-g8iu-y8mp-p4pm-w5dpyvxtin9c","domain":"tech","question":"You want to run your application on a PaaS infrastructure, and you need to be able to select both your instance type and your database. Which of the following services should you choose?","explanation":"Elastic Beanstalk will allow you to select both your instance type and your database type. EC2 is considered Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) and not Platform as a service. With Lambda and Lightsail you do not have the ability to select you instance type","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","title":"About Elastic Beanstalk"}],"answers":[{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":false}]},{"id":"024e0354-7a25-4a81-b42e-ce2af844e0e5","domain":"security","question":"Which service might you use to provide Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection to your applications running on AWS?","explanation":"AWS Shield is a managed Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection service that safeguards applications running on AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false}]},{"id":"ybx4uf1a-l9y3-aucn-tt1m-ku92d3hu5y5v","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are configuratble components of IAM?","explanation":"Users, Groups, Roles, and Permissions are integral to IAM. Authentication and Authorization are functions that IAM provides, but not actual components of it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/getting-started/","title":"IAM - Getting Started"}],"answers":[{"id":"3948d67c633d9035eaf2216ba0e1b2dc","text":"Authenticator","correct":false},{"id":"2999b7d01e6b02e94fc22c79b978d3b0","text":"Access controls","correct":false},{"id":"18ade94f5fe966167a6645362290cdcb","text":"Authorizer","correct":false},{"id":"a37ede293936e29279ed543129451ec3","text":"Groups","correct":true},{"id":"f9aae5fda8d810a29f12d1e61b4ab25f","text":"Users","correct":true},{"id":"d08ccf52b4cdd08e41cfb99ec42e0b29","text":"Permissions","correct":true},{"id":"a5cd3ed116608dac017f14c046ea56bf","text":"Roles","correct":true}]},{"id":"cykf25tw-ja73-62pe-bg44-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Broadly speaking AWS is responsible for:","explanation":"Generally speaking, AWS is responsible for security OF the cloud - meaning that it is responsible for the infrastructure (hardware and software) which is used to deliver cloud services to customers.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"e5a10169b294451720bbfc8cee548381","text":"Security both IN and OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"2245b1bb4da8871fd09d4b5b6c52555e","text":"Security IN the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"2ac2679f0084e375060c216fe7477ab4","text":"Security OF the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"17e0b507a41c19ff7684c3bf9d56497f","text":"None of security - security is up to the customer to manage","correct":false}]}]}}}}
